Hey. Hey. How are you? All good.
All right. Before we get started, I want
to start off by thanking a few people
cuz as you guys know, when we go to the
draft, a lot goes into it. It takes an
entire building and department. So, bear
with me. Obviously starting at the top
with ownership, Woody and Christopher
nothing but supportive through the whole
process, giving myself and our staff all
the resources we need. Destiny
Rodriguez, Dan Z, Rick Spielman,
obviously Coach AG and the entire
coaching staff a collaborative effort
through the whole process. Um, three to
four weeks working with them has been
awesome. Our analytics department led by
Sean Clement, Nick, Sabella, Casey
handling all the money. currently very
busy upstairs as we work through this
free agency process after the draft
which is always fun. And then our entire
scouting department. I think we have
some of the best scouts in the NFL.
Groups led by Robbie Payeyton.
say the medical staff led by Zuff,
operations staff led by AD, Bobby Mrod
and his security staff, Justice Jones,
player engagement, Haimey, the entire
business staff, and last but not least,
RIT and football developers, Chris
Miller and EWOW have done a fantastic
job kind of transitioning our IT system
um into something that I'm more familiar
with, which has really helped me through
this draft process this year, and it's
been very seamless and awesome. So with
that, I will open it to questions for
Adrian.
>> Oh, good. Let's do it.
>> Darren, why uh could you just give us
your evaluation of Club Nick and why did
you feel it was necessary to trade up
there?
>> Yeah, I felt really good about Cade. You
know, it started obviously last year
evaluating all those quarterbacks going
into this year. We had good good grades
on Cade going in this year. And then,
you know, you watch him this year, he
got hurt uh early and was playing hurt
much of the year and that team kind of
struggled, but was excited to get around
him at the combine. had a great combine
interview which kind of um sparked us to
want to get down to Clemson and work him
out and spend some more time with him
and we went down there and again it was
a great exposure being there on campus
with him in the room talking ball felt
very natural felt like there was a
connection there getting on the field
doing the workout uh showed well so felt
really good about Cade um a young player
that has a lot of experience you know
played a lot of a lot of snaps in high
school 30 and0 record in in Texas. Went
to Clemson as a young I think
17-year-old. Three-ear starter at
Clemson. Won a lot of games there. Um
unfortunately had a down year this year,
but still young, athletic with some
upside and feel really good about um
being able to get them.
>> Aaron, this is big picture, but what do
you believe you accomplished with this
with this draft? Um, number one, I think
we've been saying this um throughout the
throughout the week is, man, guys that
have won and there's a number of
different um different type of guys that
we got. So, um, when you look at today,
man, we got huge men to play for us. Um,
and you probably heard me say Mass Kicks
ass. and with with DJ um with Coupe, I
mean those guys I mean those guys are
are really good developmental um linemen
that we can have um be able to look at
the guys that we have and be able to
learn and get better. Uh we just talked
about Clubnik and and just the
experience that he has um high school as
many games as he's won um as many games
he's won in college um and he still has
a way to go to get where he needs to go.
Um, but just overall I think we did a
really good job of identifying the guys
that we love and we brought them here to
this team to be able to help us continue
to move in the direction that we want to
move.
Can I ask for actually both of you and
Darren when you take a step back and I
know you just finished up with the draft
but yeah
>> everything you've done for the last four
months you know the free agency period
you know the coaching staff changes yeah
>> you know just to kind of reboot from
last year can you describe how how much
advanced are you feeling even yourself
in your second year having you know
>> that that's that's a really good
question um because it really started
like right at the end of the year to
where and I've said this many a times
that I want to evaluate myself and see
exactly the things that I need to
improve on. And that's exactly where it
started. Right? Right after the exit
meetings with the players, I mean, I
really took a long look at the things
that I need to improve on and then how
can we move forward as a football team.
Um, and that's when everything between
men moving really intentional on the
steps that we want to take. And you
heard us say we want to be
processoriented, meaning we did not want
to miss a step. we know exactly what we
were seeing. We know exactly what the
vision was and all the steps in between
there to actually get to that vision and
we're not done yet. You know, we want to
make sure that we were very intentional
about those things. So, it started with
the coaching staff. Um, and then we got
to free agency, which, you know, we were
all happy about, and then we had the
draft, which we're happy about, and now
we have to continue to go through OTAAS
and be intentional about those things to
make sure that we get better as a
football team and as an organization.
So, um, I'm happy where we're at. We've
grown. We've grown, but we still have a
ways to go. Um, and we're going to do
everything we can to make sure we get
there.
>> Erin, how would you describe or assess
the short and long-term health of the
quarterback position
>> as far as
>> as far as right like the short term
being this year?
>> Yeah. Okay, I got you. I got you. Well,
listen, obviously we brought in Gino to
be our starter. Um, and I'm not going to
cap put a cap on him on how many years
he can play. So, I don't want to even go
into the fact of he's here for a year,
he's a, you know what I'm saying? Like,
as long as he's producing and as long as
he's the best, you know, guy for, I
mean, he's going to continue to play.
But obviously in this league, you got to
have a system where there are backups
and there are guys that are pushing the
starter and you always want to create
that type of competition. Um, listen,
I'm not going to sit here and say
exactly where where K's going to play.
The thing is those guys going to go out
there and compete, you know. So, um,
right now I like their room. I like
where it's at. The guys going to
continue to pee compete. Um, and I don't
want to cap in those guys as far as play
time and and how long they're going to
play and things like that. They're going
to go out there and um, as long as
they're competing and giving us the best
chance to win, they'll be here for us.
>> Along those lines, I think you told us
at in Arizona that you were thinking of
adding a veteran quarterback before the
draft and you didn't. Are you still did
you still think about adding a veteran
to that room because the three guys
behind Gino haven't played a ton of
football?
>> Yeah. And I remember those comments at
the at the owners meeting. We got back
and we kind of spoke as a group and
talked about and that landscape really
hasn't moved much. Um and we felt good
about that at that time and and didn't
anticipate it moving. So felt like okay
let's let's go into the draft. Let's see
where we come out. We'll reconvene and
say okay now let's look at the
landscape. Let's look at the picture.
Let's have some good discussions about
what we know we have now coming out of
the draft and kind of further evaluate
it. So, we'll see in the coming weeks.
>> Now that you're through the draft,
Darren, is this uh uh getting back to
the table with Bree? Is that something
you guys might want to do
>> potentially? I mean, I got a list of
things they're going to turn the page
from on the draft and and address next
week. That being one of them, you know,
internally discuss and we'll see where
that goes. Aaron, you I mean for both of
you actually. You talked about your
growth and stuff like that, but I'm
curious like
>> you last year you guys had only been
working with each other for like three
or four months when you went into the
draft. I'm curious if you notice a
difference this year. Now you kind of
know each other's tendencies, what you
like and things like that, like what the
kind of flow is like in the draft room
for the two of you.
>> Well, I would say mentality wise as far
as how we want this team to look. Um
like we're so much um in sync on that
and it's not like we weren't in sync
last last year. It's just the fact, man,
it's it's it's it's it feels really good
to have a partner um that sees it the
same way as you. And listen, I know that
Mooj will talk to you about where things
that he he's he has to grow. I know
things that where I have to grow, but um
as long as we continue to have um have
those conversations and making sure
we're still like moving in a direction
to where we can take this organization
where it needs to go. Um, it feels
really good. And again, it feels really
good to have someone that you can trust
that you know has your back. Um, I think
every coach, and I'm just speaking as a
head coach now, every coach in a league
will love to have a GM like that because
it's just it's all about trusting me.
>> And I can say I know last year when we
hit the ground running, although it was
fairly new, just a few months, it felt
very easy and natural. I don't remember
any times where it wasn't. We were like
feeling each other out. Obviously with
time on task we know each other even
better and we have a better
understanding and the language is
seamless. Um I can speak for myself too
just in terms of process and being more
um kind of familiar with all the faces
obviously AG but our entire staff our
coaches uh you have a better
understanding for the people and um the
question was asked earlier going into
this draft is different. It's it's
definitely
um a more comfortable feeling going in
knowing you have a whole year with your
process as we changed the entire grading
scale from from our last draft. So,
we're we're in a different scale. We're
in a different system. I I I felt much
more comfortable visualizing the board
this year and kind of knowing how it was
going to fall. Um and feel really good
about um where we're at as a whole
staff.
>> What went into that? The the changing of
the Is it similar what you did in
Denver? like from what like I guess what
goes into
>> actually so last year you get here it's
hard to make an overhaul of systems and
scales and stuff. So you kind of just
dive in and say okay let's let's figure
it out as we go and and and we adapted
and adjusted to the current group and
you kind of figure it out and then once
you get through the draft say okay in
the offseason we're going to get
together collect collectively as a group
and we actually created our own scale. I
I had all of my scouts pitch different
ideas. I mean, it was several weeks of a
process and we had a lot of discussion
and cuz we've all had different
experiences, different scales, but we
created our own with our own color
schemes, our own number schemes. Had a
lot of discussion about it. Um, I would
say enhanced the systems,
>> laid out the process for the whole year
for everyone. And in doing so, I I think
a lot of guys feel really good about it.
And I think the result was pretty good
and we feel good about um
>> I just want with Darren I just want to
clarify I don't want to misinterpret
something you just said about Greece
fall you said potentially
>> start I I just want to be clear because
it sounded
>> Yeah.
>> Are you going to start the box again or
or potentially I don't know what that
means.
>> I anticipate I anticipate um addressing
the Bree Hall contract stuff. Um I got a
list of things to get to next week. That
being one of them. I want to have
discussions internally, have discussions
with Bree's party before saying much
more. But yeah, I anticipate kind of
turning my attention to Bree and that
contract situation.
>> Based off of your conversations with
with Bree and and his representatives, I
know in a perfect world you guys figure
something out and it works long term.
When you did tag him though, were you
under the impression he would play on
the tag if if you guys came?
>> I haven't had a lot of discussions since
the tag with them. I think we made a
good attempt to get something done. we
weren't able to and we were like, "Okay,
we'll use the tag for now knowing that
we have time." And since then, we both
respected the space and um thankful to
his party, they've allowed me to just
focus my attention on the draft. So,
>> I'm curious,
>> last one,
>> like the first two picks, right? Y
>> do you do you feel the need to talk to a
Mason Taylor or a Will McDonald who
might be saying, "Huh, they just drafted
someone I play the same position as. How
does this affect me?" Do do you reach
out to those guys or will you when you
see them in the building? How do you
know that?
>> Yeah, I think every player on this team
knows that like we're building
competition and they they want that
because it only makes them better. So, I
don't think there's a need to be able to
call each player, oh, we drafted a guy.
You know, those listen, those guys know
that we're going to do whatever we have
to do to get this team to be a better
team. And you might draft guys in in the
same position, but that doesn't mean
that, you know, they're attacking their
we're attacking, you know, who they are
as a as a player. It's just me, man.
We're trying to fill this team with the
best players that we can. And also, man,
two tight ends can play, three tight
ends can play, you know. So, um I think
the players understand that. And I think
that's just across the league that
that's just what it is. So, um neither
one of those guys had that I feel like I
need to call them. Um and they just know
they're going to compete for their jobs.
>> Thanks everybody. So, not one really
good argument. Not all once.
>> Say it again.
>> Knock down drag out argument. Not one
argument
>> with us.